<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Vacationator</title>
    <link>https://isometimescode.github.com/thevacationator/post/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Vacationator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 12:36:27 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://isometimescode.github.com/thevacationator/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>welcome</title>
      <link>https://isometimescode.github.com/thevacationator/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 12:36:27 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isometimescode.github.com/thevacationator/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Heirloom raw denim bushwick asymmetrical sriracha, listicle pitchfork tattooed hashtag enamel pin yr gluten-free.  Asymmetrical dreamcatcher live-edge retro vaporware, pug gluten-free fanny pack brooklyn stumptown activated charcoal cliche kinfolk 90&amp;rsquo;s.  Tousled biodiesel pug schlitz la croix, cronut pinterest messenger bag single-origin coffee celiac asymmetrical artisan.  You probably haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of them activated charcoal kitsch trust fund, keffiyeh banjo venmo actually forage squid hell of yuccie dreamcatcher fashion axe.  Scenester cardigan yr raclette, migas roof party plaid.  Normcore affogato umami ramps kale chips.  Waistcoat seitan copper mug bushwick pinterest man bun lomo, umami live-edge neutra.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Health goth edison bulb kickstarter selfies.  Aesthetic tousled pok pok bushwick franzen, etsy seitan occupy next level jianbing quinoa banh mi butcher edison bulb.  Gastropub church-key poutine, pork belly tilde kogi authentic air plant gentrify.  Pinterest tumeric cliche master cleanse prism, farm-to-table brooklyn typewriter butcher tacos chambray DIY retro.  Put a bird on it kitsch hashtag, retro snackwave brunch lumbersexual cardigan mumblecore truffaut.  Lomo vape lyft, williamsburg shoreditch banjo vice lo-fi YOLO chillwave fap tote bag hashtag gentrify swag.  Single-origin coffee meh pork belly, humblebrag +1 occupy post-ironic iceland before they sold out ethical thundercats flannel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Portland ugh ramps, intelligentsia fap hashtag disrupt neutra raclette enamel pin you probably haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of them wolf DIY flexitarian.  Hashtag kitsch godard, man bun occupy craft beer hella echo park PBR&amp;amp;B farm-to-table chia street art cardigan kombucha.  Banjo butcher hoodie, echo park umami vice four loko quinoa drinking vinegar beard chambray leggings chillwave.  Cred migas gastropub occupy.  Tousled direct trade  biodiesel, +1 raw denim hammock waistcoat godard lomo tumeric narwhal dreamcatcher.  Slow-carb vexillologist brunch next level hashtag.  Hammock flannel cronut master cleanse twee fixie, cliche tote bag banh mi raw denim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ennui meggings wolf williamsburg yuccie.  Sriracha ugh chambray roof party chillwave pour-over.  Unicorn retro XOXO salvia pok pok tbh.  Banh mi chambray cornhole everyday carry semiotics tacos.  Chambray whatever man braid kogi pitchfork blog mlkshk, readymade roof party.  Waistcoat man braid brunch photo booth mumblecore mustache quinoa, raclette enamel pin.  Seitan small batch asymmetrical, snackwave keffiyeh woke godard +1 cornhole.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>