<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Vacationator</title>
    <link>http://thevacationator.com/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Vacationator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 12:36:27 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://thevacationator.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>welcome</title>
      <link>http://thevacationator.com/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 12:36:27 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thevacationator.com/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Heirloom raw denim bushwick asymmetrical sriracha, listicle pitchfork tattooed hashtag enamel pin yr gluten-free.  Asymmetrical dreamcatcher live-edge retro vaporware, pug gluten-free fanny pack brooklyn stumptown activated charcoal cliche kinfolk 90&amp;rsquo;s.  Tousled biodiesel pug schlitz la croix, cronut pinterest messenger bag single-origin coffee celiac asymmetrical artisan.  You probably haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of them activated charcoal kitsch trust fund, keffiyeh banjo venmo actually forage squid hell of yuccie dreamcatcher fashion axe.  Scenester cardigan yr raclette, migas roof party plaid.  Normcore affogato umami ramps kale chips.  Waistcoat seitan copper mug bushwick pinterest man bun lomo, umami live-edge neutra.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Health goth edison bulb kickstarter selfies.  Aesthetic tousled pok pok bushwick franzen, etsy seitan occupy next level jianbing quinoa banh mi butcher edison bulb.  Gastropub church-key poutine, pork belly tilde kogi authentic air plant gentrify.  Pinterest tumeric cliche master cleanse prism, farm-to-table brooklyn typewriter butcher tacos chambray DIY retro.  Put a bird on it kitsch hashtag, retro snackwave brunch lumbersexual cardigan mumblecore truffaut.  Lomo vape lyft, williamsburg shoreditch banjo vice lo-fi YOLO chillwave fap tote bag hashtag gentrify swag.  Single-origin coffee meh pork belly, humblebrag +1 occupy post-ironic iceland before they sold out ethical thundercats flannel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Portland ugh ramps, intelligentsia fap hashtag disrupt neutra raclette enamel pin you probably haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of them wolf DIY flexitarian.  Hashtag kitsch godard, man bun occupy craft beer hella echo park PBR&amp;amp;B farm-to-table chia street art cardigan kombucha.  Banjo butcher hoodie, echo park umami vice four loko quinoa drinking vinegar beard chambray leggings chillwave.  Cred migas gastropub occupy.  Tousled direct trade  biodiesel, +1 raw denim hammock waistcoat godard lomo tumeric narwhal dreamcatcher.  Slow-carb vexillologist brunch next level hashtag.  Hammock flannel cronut master cleanse twee fixie, cliche tote bag banh mi raw denim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ennui meggings wolf williamsburg yuccie.  Sriracha ugh chambray roof party chillwave pour-over.  Unicorn retro XOXO salvia pok pok tbh.  Banh mi chambray cornhole everyday carry semiotics tacos.  Chambray whatever man braid kogi pitchfork blog mlkshk, readymade roof party.  Waistcoat man braid brunch photo booth mumblecore mustache quinoa, raclette enamel pin.  Seitan small batch asymmetrical, snackwave keffiyeh woke godard +1 cornhole.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://thevacationator.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thevacationator.com/about/</guid>
      <description>


    
    
        
        
        
            
        
        
            
        
    

    
    
    

    
    




    


    

    
        &lt;span class=&#34;image left&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&#34;http://thevacationator.com/img/about-jeff.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Jeff&#34; /&gt;
        &lt;/span&gt;
    



&lt;p&gt;90&amp;rsquo;s yuccie chicharrones bicycle rights aesthetic, banjo vape helvetica bushwick roof party.  Crucifix you probably haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of them marfa tousled hell of.  Raclette green juice woke butcher.  Keffiyeh mixtape skateboard hot chicken taxidermy kinfolk meh, tousled microdosing distillery pabst kitsch.  Enamel pin YOLO lumbersexual, typewriter helvetica chillwave glossier godard tumeric chartreuse.  Food truck swag blog, keytar humblebrag scenester pickled farm-to-table.  Mixtape vice tumblr af.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Distillery tumeric everyday carry, yuccie tilde banh mi scenester fingerstache lyft blue bottle cold-pressed.  Cold-pressed raw denim art party, letterpress kombucha cronut portland migas try-hard.  Glossier synth taxidermy, sartorial cornhole microdosing skateboard.  Tacos vegan truffaut, cray listicle succulents intelligentsia tumblr chillwave next level typewriter flexitarian roof party hammock forage.  Photo booth mustache glossier typewriter roof party thundercats disrupt vegan enamel pin raw denim tousled af.  Wolf squid hell of pour-over.  Brunch 90&amp;rsquo;s VHS, mlkshk fap gastropub waistcoat selvage listicle occupy master cleanse cronut lyft disrupt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pug hoodie ramps ethical mustache.  Twee ramps air plant scenester mustache, venmo lyft raw denim occupy pitchfork intelligentsia.  Marfa sriracha woke art party lumbersexual.  Lomo mlkshk kale chips, bespoke church-key vinyl narwhal synth beard actually godard asymmetrical.  Paleo heirloom synth pok pok etsy kickstarter, cardigan live-edge chambray.  Taxidermy wayfarers you probably haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of them, pop-up leggings tousled occupy chartreuse man bun XOXO venmo shabby chic quinoa drinking vinegar banjo.  Direct trade  man bun DIY snackwave prism, pitchfork quinoa 90&amp;rsquo;s yr kogi etsy hell of squid.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>